export interface Question {
  question: string
  link?: string
  difficulty: string
  category: string
  solution: string
  dailyChallenge?: Date
}

const tableData: Question[] = [
    {
      question: "Coin Change",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "coin-change.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Level Sum of a Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-level-sum-of-a-binary-tree/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Tree",
      solution: "maximum-level-sum-of-a-binary-tree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-15"),
    },
    {
      question: "Make Array Strictly Increasing",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/make-array-strictly-increasing/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "make-array-strictly-increasing.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-17"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Increasing Paths in a Grid",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-increasing-paths-in-a-grid/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-18"),
      solution: "number-of-increasing-path-in-a-grid.py"
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Ways to Reorder Array to Get Same BST",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-ways-to-reorder-array-to-get-same-bst/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Math",
      solution: "get-the-same-bst.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-16"),
    },
    {
      question: "Shortest Path in Binary Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/shortest-path-in-binary-matrix/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "shortest-path-in-binary-matrix.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-01"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Detonate the Maximum Bombs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/detonate-the-maximum-bombs/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "detonate-the-maximum-bombs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-02"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Time Needed to Inform All Employees",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/time-needed-to-inform-all-employees/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "time-needed-to-inform-all-employees.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-03"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Number of Provinces",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-provinces/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "number-of-provinces.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-04"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Check If It Is a Straight Line",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-it-is-a-straight-line/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Math",
      solution: "check-if-it-is-a-straight-line.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-05"),
    },
    {
      question: "Can Make Arithmetic Progression From Sequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/can-make-arithmetic-progression-from-sequence/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "can-make-arithmetic-progression-from-sequence.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-06"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Minimum Flips to Make a OR b Equal to c",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-flips-to-make-a-or-b-equal-to-c/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Bit Manipulation",
      solution: "minimum-flips-to-make-a-or-b-equal-to-c.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-07"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count Negative Numbers in a Sorted Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-negative-numbers-in-a-sorted-matrix/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "count-negative-numbers-in-a-sorted-matrix.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-08"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Smallest Letter Greater Than Target",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-smallest-letter-greater-than-target/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Binary Search",
      solution: "find-smallest-letter-greater-than-target.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-09"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Value at a Given Index in a Bounded Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-value-at-a-given-index-in-a-bounded-array/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Binary Search",
      solution: "maximum-value-at-a-given-index-in-a-bounded-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-10"),
    },//
    {
      question: "Snapshot Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/snapshot-array/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "snapshot-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-11"),
    },
    {
      question: "Summary Ranges",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/summary-ranges/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Interval",
      solution: "summary-ranges.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-12"),
    },
    {
      question: "Equal Row and Column Pairs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/equal-row-and-column-pairs/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "equal-row-and-column-pairs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-13"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Absolute Difference in BST",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-absolute-difference-in-bst/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Tree",
      solution: "minimum-absolute-difference-in-bst.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-14"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Highest Altitude",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-highest-altitude/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "find-the-highest-altitude.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-19"),
    },
    {
      question: "K Radius Subarray Averages",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/k-radius-subarray-averages/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "k-radius-subarray-averages.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-20"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Cost to Make Array Equal",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-cost-to-make-array-equal/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Binary Search",
      solution: "minimum-cost-to-make-array-equal.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-21"),
    },
    {
      question: "Painting the Walls",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/painting-the-walls/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "painting-the-walls.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-14"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Value of the Partition",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-value-of-the-partition/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "find-the-value-of-the-partition.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Total Distance Traveled",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/total-distance-traveled/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "total-distance-traveled.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock with Transaction Fee",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-transaction-fee/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-transaction-fee.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-22"),
    },
    {
      question: "X of a Kind in a Deck of Cards",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/x-of-a-kind-in-a-deck-of-cards/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "x-of-a-kind-in-a-deck-of-cards.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Product of Three Numbers",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-of-three-numbers/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      solution: "maximum-product-of-three-numbers.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Arithmetic Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-arithmetic-subsequence/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "longest-arithmetic-subsequence.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-23"),
    },
    {
      question: "Tallest Billboard",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/tallest-billboard/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "tallest-billboard.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-24"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count All Possible Routes",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-all-possible-routes/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "count-all-possible-routes.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-25"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Beautiful Pairs",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-beautiful-pairs/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "number-of-beautiful-pairs.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Operations to Make the Integer Zero",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-operations-to-make-the-integer-zero/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Bit Manipulation",
      solution: "minimum-operations-to-make-the-integer-zero.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Total Cost to Hire K Workers",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/total-cost-to-hire-k-workers/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Priority Queue",
      solution: "total-cost-to-hire-k-workers.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-26"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Ways to Split Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-ways-to-split-array/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "number-of-ways-to-split-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "All Divisions With the Highest Score of a Binary Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/all-divisions-with-the-highest-score-of-a-binary-array/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "all-divisions-with-the-highest-score-of-a-binary-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Find K Pairs with Smallest Sums",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-k-pairs-with-smallest-sums/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Priority Queue",
      solution: "find-k-pairs-with-smallest-sums.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-27"),
    },
    {
      question: "Guess Number Higher or Lower II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/guess-number-higher-or-lower-ii/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dyamic Programming",
      solution: "guess-number-higher-or-lower-ii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Path with Maximum Probability",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/path-with-maximum-probability/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "path-with-maximum-probability.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-28"),
    },
    {
      question: "Shortest Path to Get All Keys",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/shortest-path-to-get-all-keys/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "shortest-path-to-get-all-keys.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-29"),
    },
    {
      question: "Last Day Where You Can Still Cross",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/last-day-where-you-can-still-cross/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "last-day-where-you-can-still-cross.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-06-30"),
    },
    {
      question: "Fair Distribution of Cookies",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/fair-distribution-of-cookies/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Backtracking",
      solution: "fair-distribution-of-cookies.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-01"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Number of Achievable Transfer Requests",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-achievable-transfer-requests/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Backtracking",
      solution: "maximum-number-of-achievable-transfer-requests.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-02"),
    },
    {
      question: "Buddy Strings",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/buddy-strings/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "buddy-strings.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-03"),
    },
    {
      question: "Single-Threaded CPU",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-threaded-cpu/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Priority Queue",
      solution: "single-threaded-cpu.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Single Number II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-number-ii/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "single-number-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-04"),
    },
    {
      question: "Remove Zero Sum Consecutive Nodes from Linked List",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-zero-sum-consecutive-nodes-from-linked-list/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Linked List",
      solution: "remove-zero-sum-consecutive-nodes-from-linked-list.py",
    },    
    {
      question: "Longest Subarray of 1's After Deleting One Element",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-subarray-of-1s-after-deleting-one-element/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      solution: "longest-subarray-of-1s-after-deleting-one-element.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-05"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Size Subarray Sum",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-size-subarray-sum/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      solution: "minimum-size-subarray-sum.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-06"),
    },
    {
      question: "Combinations",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combinations/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Backtracking",
      solution: "combinations.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-01"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximize the Confusion of an Exam",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximize-the-confusion-of-an-exam/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      solution: "maximize-the-confusion-of-an-exam.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-07"),
    },
    {
      question: "Put Marbles in Bags",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/put-marbles-in-bags/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Math",
      solution: "put-marbles-in-bags.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-08"),
    },
    {
      question: "Substring With Largest Variance",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/substring-with-largest-variance/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "substring-with-largest-variance.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-09"),
    },
    {
      question: "Subarray Sum Equals K",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subarray-sum-equals-k/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "subarray-sum-equals-k.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Depth of Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "minimum-depth-of-binary-tree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-10"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Depth of Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "maximum-depth-of-binary-tree.py",
    },
    {
      question: "All Nodes Distance K in Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/all-nodes-distance-k-in-binary-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "all-nodes-distance-k-in-binary-tree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-11"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Eventual Safe States",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-eventual-safe-states/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-eventual-safe-states.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-12"),
    },
    {
      question: "Course Schedule",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "course-schedule.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-13"),
    },
    {
      question: "Course Schedule II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule-ii/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "course-schedule-ii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Subarray Sum with One Deletion",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray-sum-with-one-deletion/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-subarray-sum-with-one-deletion.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Verifying an Alien Dictionary",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/verifying-an-alien-dictionary/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "verifying-an-alien-dictionary.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Decode String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/decode-string/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "decode-string.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Arithmetic Subsequence of Given Difference",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-arithmetic-subsequence-of-given-difference/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-arithmetic-subsequence-of-given-difference.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-14"),
    },
    {
      question: "Insert Interval",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/insert-interval/",
      category: "Interval",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "insert-interval.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Increasing Path in a Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-path-in-a-matrix/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "longest-increasing-path-in-a-matrix.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Palindrome Partitioning",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-partitioning/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "palindrome-partitioning.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Valid Sudoku",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-sudoku/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "valid-sudoku.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Min Stack",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-stack/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "min-stack.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Detect Squares",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/detect-squares/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "detect-squares.py",
    },
    {
      question: "House Robber II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber-ii/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "house-robber-ii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Target Sum",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/target-sum/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "target-sum.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Valid Parenthesis String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parenthesis-string/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "valid-parenthesis-string.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Number of Events That Can Be Attended II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-events-that-can-be-attended-ii/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "maximum-number-of-events-that-can-be-attended-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-15"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Number of Events That Can Be Attended",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-events-that-can-be-attended/",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-number-of-events-that-can-be-attended.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Daily Temperatures",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/daily-temperatures/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "daily-temperatures.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Reconstruct Itinerary",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reconstruct-itinerary/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "reconstruct-itinerary.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-14")
    },
    {
      question: "Construct Binary Tree from Preorder and Inorder Traversal",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Merge k Sorted Lists",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-k-sorted-lists/",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "merge-k-sorted-lists.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Non-overlapping Intervals",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/non-overlapping-intervals/",
      category: "Interval",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "non-overlapping-intervals.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-19")
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Subsequences That Satisfy the Given Sum Condition",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-subsequences-that-satisfy-the-given-sum-condition/",
      category: "Pointers",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "number-of-subsequences-that-satisfy-the-given-sum-condition.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Smallest Sufficient Team",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/smallest-sufficient-team/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "smallest-sufficient-team.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-16"),
    },
    {
      question: "Valid Parentheses",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "valid-parentheses.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Connecting Graph III",
      link: "https://www.lintcode.com/problem/591/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "union-find-algorithm.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Beauty of an Array After Applying Operation",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-beauty-of-an-array-after-applying-operation/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-beauty-of-an-array-after-applying-operation.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Sum of Squares of Special Elements",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-squares-of-special-elements/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "sum-of-squares-of-special-elements.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Index of a Valid Split",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-index-of-a-valid-split/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-index-of-a-valid-split.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Add Two Numbers II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/add-two-numbers-ii/",
      category: "Linked List",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "add-two-numbers-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-17"),
    },
    {
      question: "Length of the Longest Valid Substring",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/length-of-the-longest-valid-substring/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "length-of-the-longest-valid-substring.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Partition Labels",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-labels/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "partition-labels.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Pow(x, n)",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/powx-n/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "powx-n.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-24")
    },
    {
      question: "Valid Palindrome II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-palindrome-ii/",
      category: "Pointers",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "valid-palindrome-ii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Count Good Nodes in Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree.py",
    },
    {
      question: "LRU Cache",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lru-cache/",
      category: "Linked List",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "lru-cache.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-18"),
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Palindromic Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-subsequence/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-palindromic-subsequence.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Common Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-subsequence/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-common-subsequence.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Reverse Linked List",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list/",
      category: "Linked List",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "reverse-linked-list.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Distinct Prime Factors of Product of Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/distinct-prime-factors-of-product-of-array/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "distinct-prime-factors-of-product-of-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Asteroid Collision",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/asteroid-collision/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "asteroid-collision.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-20")
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Longest Increasing Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-longest-increasing-subsequence/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "number-of-longest-increasing-subsequence.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-21")
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-increasing-subsequence.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Is Graph Bipartite?",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-graph-bipartite/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "is-graph-bipartite.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Possible Bipartition",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/possible-bipartition/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "possible-bipartition.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Knight Probability in Chessboard",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/knight-probability-in-chessboard/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "knight-probability-in-chessboard.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-22")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimize Maximum of Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimize-maximum-of-array/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimize-maximum-of-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "All Possible Full Binary Trees",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/all-possible-full-binary-trees/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "all-possible-full-binary-trees.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-23")
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Enclaves",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-enclaves/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "number-of-enclaves.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Fruit Into Baskets",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/fruit-into-baskets/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "fruit-into-baskets.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Peak Index in a Mountain Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/peak-index-in-a-mountain-array/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "peak-index-in-a-mountain-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-25")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Speed to Arrive on Time",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-speed-to-arrive-on-time/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-speed-to-arrive-on-time.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-26")
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Running Time of N Computers",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-running-time-of-n-computers/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "maximum-running-time-of-n-computers.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-27")
    },
    {
      question: "Predict the Winner",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/predict-the-winner/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "predict-the-winner.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-28")
    },
    {
      question: "Soup Servings",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/soup-servings/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "soup-servings.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-29")
    },
    {
      question: "Strange Printer",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/strange-printer/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "strange-printer.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-30")
    },
    {
      question: "Invert Binary Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/invert-binary-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "invert-binary-tree.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Shortest Completing Word",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/shortest-completing-word/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "shortest-completing-word.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum ASCII Delete Sum for Two Strings",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-ascii-delete-sum-for-two-strings/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-ascii-delete-sum-for-two-strings.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-07-31")
    },
    {
      question: "Degree of an Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/degree-of-an-array/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "degree-of-an-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Permutations",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "permutations.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-02")
    },
    {
      question: "Permutations II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations-ii/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "permutations-ii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Letter Combinations of a Phone Number",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-03")
    },
    {
      question: "Word Break",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-break/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "word-break.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-04")
    },
    {
      question: "Restore IP Addresses",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/restore-ip-addresses/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "restore-ip-addresses.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Unique Binary Search Trees II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-binary-search-trees-ii/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "unique-binary-search-trees-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-05")
    },
    {
      question: "Unique Binary Search Trees",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-binary-search-trees/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "unique-binary-search-trees.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock with Cooldown",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-cooldown/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-cooldown.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Music Playlists",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-music-playlists/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "number-of-music-playlists.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-06")
    },
    {
      question: "Faulty Keyboard",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/faulty-keyboard/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "faulty-keyboard.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Check if it is Possible to Split Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-it-is-possible-to-split-array/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "check-if-it-is-possible-to-split-array.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Safest Path in a Grid",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-safest-path-in-a-grid/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-the-safest-path-in-a-grid.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Search a 2D Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-a-2d-matrix/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "search-a-2d-matrix.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-07")
    },
    {
      question: "Count Primes",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-primes/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "count-primes.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Combination Sum III",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-iii/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "combination-sum-iii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Search in Rotated Sorted Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "search-in-rotated-sorted-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-08")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimize the Maximum Difference of Pairs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimize-the-maximum-difference-of-pairs/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimize-the-maximum-difference-of-pairs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-09")
    },
    {
      question: "Search in Rotated Sorted Array II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array-ii/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "search-in-rotated-sorted-array-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-10")
    },
    {
      question: "Path Sum III",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/path-sum-iii/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "path-sum-iii.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Coin Change II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change-ii/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "coin-change-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-11")
    },
    {
      question: "Unique Path II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-path-ii/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "unique-path-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-12")
    },
    {
      question: "Check if There is a Valid Partition For The Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-there-is-a-valid-partition-for-the-array/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "check-if-there-is-a-valid-partition-for-the-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-13")
    },
    {
      question: "Kth Largest Element in an Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      solution: "kth-largest-element-in-an-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-14")
    },
    {
      question: "Partition List",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-list/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Linked List",
      solution: "partition-list.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-15")
    },
    {
      question: "Sliding Window Maximum",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sliding-window-maximum/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Stack",
      solution: "sliding-window-maximum.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-16")
    },
    {
      question: "01 Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/01-matrix/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "01-matrix.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-17")
    },
    {
      question: "Maximal Network Rank",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximal-network-rank/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "maximal-network-rank.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-18")
    },
    {
      question: "Find Critical and Pseudo-Critical Edges in Minimum Spanning Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-critical-and-pseudo-critical-edges-in-minimum-spanning-tree/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "find-critical-and-pseudo-critical-edges-in-minimum-spanning-tree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-19")
    },
    {
      question: "Sorting Three Groups",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sorting-three-groups/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "sorting-three-groups.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Sort Items by Groups Respecting Dependencies",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-items-by-groups-respecting-dependencies/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Graph",
      solution: "sort-items-by-groups-respecting-dependencies.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-20")
    },
    {
      question: "Repeated Substring Pattern",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/repeated-substring-pattern/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "repeated-substring-pattern.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-21")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Number of Days to Make m Bouquets",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-days-to-make-m-bouquets/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Binary Search",
      solution: "minimum-number-of-days-to-make-m-bouquets.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Excel Sheet Column Title",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/excel-sheet-column-title/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Math",
      solution: "excel-sheet-column-title.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-22")
    },
    {
      question: "Reorganize String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reorganize-string/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      solution: "reorganize-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-23")
    },
    {
      question: "Text Justification",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/text-justification/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "text-justification.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-24")
    },
    {
      question: "Interleaving String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/interleaving-string/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "interleaving-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-25")
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Length of Pair Chain",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-length-of-pair-chain/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "maximum-length-of-pair-chain.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-26")
    },
    {
      question: "Frog Jump",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/frog-jump/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "frog-jump.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-27")
    },
    {
      question: "Implement Stack using Queues",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-stack-using-queues/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      solution: "implement-stack-using-queues.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-28")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Penalty for a Shop",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-penalty-for-a-shop/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Greedy",
      solution: "minimum-penalty-for-a-shop.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-29")
    },
    {
      question: "Super Egg Drop",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/super-egg-drop/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "super-egg-drop.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Replacements to Sort the Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-replacements-to-sort-the-array/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Greedy",
      solution: "minimum-replacements-to-sort-the-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-30")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Number of Taps to Open to Water a Garden",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-taps-to-open-to-water-a-garden/",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "minimum-number-of-taps-to-open-to-water-a-garden.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-08-31")
    },
    {
      question: "Counting Bits",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/counting-bits/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "counting-bits.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-01")
    },
    {
      question: "Extra Characters in a String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/extra-characters-in-a-string/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "extra-characters-in-a-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-02")
    },
    {
      question: "Unique Path",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-path/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      solution: "unique-path.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-03")
    },
    {
      question: "Linked List Cycle",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle/",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      category: "Linked List",
      solution: "linked-list-cycle.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-04")
    },
    {
      question: "Copy List With Random Pointer",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/copy-list-with-random-pointer/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Linked List",
      solution: "copy-list-with-random-pointer.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-05")
    },
    {
      question: "Split Linked List in Parts",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/split-linked-list-in-parts/",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      category: "Linked List",
      solution: "split-linked-list-in-parts.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-06")
    },
    {
      question: "Reverse Linked List II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list-ii/",
      category: "Linked List",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "reverse-linked-list-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-07")
    },
    {
      question: "Pascal's Triangle",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pascals-triangle/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "pascals-triangle.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-08")
    },
    {
      question: "Combination Sum IV",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-iv/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "combination-sum-iv.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-09")
    },
    {
      question: "Count All Valid Pickup and Delivery Options",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-all-valid-pickup-and-delivery-options/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "count-all-valid-pickup-and-delivery-options.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-10")
    },
    {
      question: "Group the People Given the Group Size They Belong To",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/group-the-people-given-the-group-size-they-belong-to/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "group-the-people-given-the-group-size-they-belong-to.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-11")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Deletions to Make Character Frequencies Unique",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-deletions-to-make-character-frequencies-unique/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-deletions-to-make-character-frequencies-unique.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-12")
    },
    {
      question: "Candy",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/candy/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "candy.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-13")
    },
    {
      question: "Min Cost to Connect All Points",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-cost-to-connect-all-points/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "min-cost-to-connect-all-points.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-15")
    },
    {
      question: "Path With Minimum Effort",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/path-with-minimum-effort/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "path-with-minimum-effort.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-16")
    },
    {
      question: "Shortest Path Visiting All Nodes",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/shortest-path-visiting-all-nodes/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "shortest-path-visiting-all-nodes.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-17")
    },
    {
      question: "The K Weakest Rows in a Matrix",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/the-k-weakest-rows-in-a-matrix/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "the-k-weakest-rows-in-a-matrix.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-18")
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Duplicate Number",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-duplicate-number/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-the-duplicate-number.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-19")
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Operations to Reduce X to Zero",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-operations-to-reduce-x-to-zero/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-operations-to-reduce-x-to-zero.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-20")
    },
    {
      question: "Median of Two Sorted Arrarys",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/median-of-two-sorted-arrays/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "median-of-two-sorted-arrays.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-21")
    },
    {
      question: "Is Subsequence",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-subsequence/",
      category: "Pointers",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "is-subsequence.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-22")
    },
    {
      question: "Longest String Chain",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-string-chain/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-string-chain.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-23")
    },
    {
      question: "Champagne Tower",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/champagne-tower/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "champagne-tower.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-24")
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Difference",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-difference/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "find-the-difference.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-25")
    },
    {
      question: "Remove Duplicate Letters",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-duplicate-letters/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "remove-duplicate-letters.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-26")
    },
    {
      question: "Decoded String at Index",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/decoded-string-at-index/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "decoded-string-at-index.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-27")
    },
    {
      question: "Sort Array By Parity",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-array-by-parity/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "sort-array-by-parity.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-28")
    },
    {
      question: "Monotonic Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/monotonic-array/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "monotonic-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-29")
    },
    {
      question: "132 Pattern",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/132-pattern/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "132-pattern.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-09-30")
    },
    {
      question: "Sort List",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-list/",
      category: "Linked List",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "sort-list.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Reverse Words in a String III",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-words-in-a-string-iii/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "reverse-words-in-a-string-iii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-01"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Operations to Collect Elements",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-operations-to-collect-elements/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "minimum-operations-to-collect-elements.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Number of Operations to Make Array Empty",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-operations-to-make-array-empty/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-number-of-operations-to-make-array-empty.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Split Array Into Maximum Number of Subarrays",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/split-array-into-maximum-number-of-subarrays/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "split-array-into-maximum-number-of-subarrays.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Number of K-Divisible Components",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-k-divisible-components/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "maximum-number-of-k-divisible-components.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Remove Colored Pieces if Both Neighbors are the Same Color",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-colored-pieces-if-both-neighbors-are-the-same-color/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "remove-colored-pieces-if-both-neighbors-are-the-same-color.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-02"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Path Quality of a Graph",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-path-quality-of-a-graph/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "maximum-path-quality-of-a-graph.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Good Pairs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-good-pairs/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "number-of-good-pairs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-03"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Sum Circular Subarray",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-sum-circular-subarray/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-sum-circular-subarray.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Snakes and Ladders",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/snakes-and-ladders/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "snakes-and-ladders.py",
    },
    {
      question: "IPO",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/ipo/",
      category: "Heap / Priority Queue",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "ipo.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Design Hashmap",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-hashmap/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "design-hashmap.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-04"),
    },
    {
      question: "Majority Element II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element-ii/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "majority-element-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-05"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Genetic Mutation",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-genetic-mutation/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-genetic-mutation.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Integer Break",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/integer-break/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "integer-break.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-06"),
    },
    {
      question: "Build Array Where You Can Find The Maximum Exactly K Comparisons",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/build-array-where-you-can-find-the-maximum-exactly-k-comparisons/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "build-array-where-you-can-find-the-maximum-exactly-k-comparisons.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-07"),
    },
    {
      question: "Max Dot Product of Two Subsequences",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-dot-product-of-two-subsequences/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "max-dot-product-of-two-subsequences.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-08"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find First and Last Position of Element in Sorted Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-first-and-last-position-of-element-in-sorted-array/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-first-and-last-position-of-element-in-sorted-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-09"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Number of Operations to Make Array Continuous",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-operations-to-make-array-continuous/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "minimum-number-of-operations-to-make-array-continuous.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-10"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Ways to Reorder Array to Get Same BST",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-flowers-in-full-bloom/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "number-of-flowers-in-full-bloom.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-11"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find in Mountain Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-in-mountain-array/",
      category: "Binary Search",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "find-in-mountain-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-12"),
    },
    {
      question: "Min Cost Climbing Stairs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-cost-climbing-stairs/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "min-cost-climbing-stairs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-13"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Ways to Stay in the Same Place After Some Steps",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-ways-to-stay-in-the-same-place-after-some-steps/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "number-of-ways-to-stay-in-the-same-place-after-some-steps.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-15"),
    },
    {
      question: "Pascal's Triangle II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pascals-triangle-ii/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "pascals-triangle-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-16"),
    },
    {
      question: "Validate Binary Tree Nodes",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-tree-nodes/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "validate-binary-tree-nodes.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-17"),
    },
    {
      question: "Parallel Courses III",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/parallel-courses-iii/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "parallel-courses-iii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-18"),
    },
    {
      question: "Backspace String Compare",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/backspace-string-compare/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "backspace-string-compare.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-19"),
    },
    {
      question: "Flatten Nested List Iterator",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/flatten-nested-list-iterator/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "flatten-nested-list-iterator.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-20"),
    },
    {
      question: "Constrained Subsequence Sum",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/constrained-subsequence-sum/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "constrained-subsequence-sum.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-21"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Score of a Good Subarray",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-score-of-a-good-subarray/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "maximum-score-of-a-good-subarray.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-22"),
    },
    {
      question: "Power of Four",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/power-of-four/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "power-of-four.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-23"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Largest Value in Each Tree Row",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-largest-value-in-each-tree-row/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-largest-value-in-each-tree-row.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-24"),
    },
    {
      question: "K-th Symbol in Grammar",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/k-th-symbol-in-grammar/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "k-th-symbol-in-grammar.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-25"),
    },
    {
      question: "Binary Trees With Factors",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-trees-with-factors/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "binary-trees-with-factors.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-26"),
    },
    {
      question: "Longest Palindromic Substring",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "longest-palindromic-substring.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-27"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count Vowels Permutation",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-vowels-permutation/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "count-vowels-permutation.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-28"),
    },
    {
      question: "Poor Pigs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/poor-pigs/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "poor-pigs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-29"),
    },
    {
      question: "Sort Integers by The Number of 1 Bits",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-integers-by-the-number-of-1-bits/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "sort-integers-by-the-number-of-1-bits.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-30"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find The Original Array of Prefix Xor",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-original-array-of-prefix-xor/",
      category: "Bit Manipulation",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-the-original-array-of-prefix-xor.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-10-31"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Mode in Binary Search Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-mode-in-binary-search-tree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "find-mode-in-binary-search-tree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-01"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count Nodes Equal to Average of Subtree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-nodes-equal-to-average-of-subtree/",
      category: "Tree",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "count-nodes-equal-to-average-of-subtree.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-02"),
    },
    {
      question: "Build an Array With Stack Operations",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/build-an-array-with-stack-operations/",
      category: "Stack",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "build-an-array-with-stack-operations.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-03"),
    },
    {
      question: "Last Moment Before All Ants Fall Out of a Plank",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/last-moment-before-all-ants-fall-out-of-a-plank/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "last-moment-before-all-ants-fall-out-of-a-plank.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-04"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find the Winner of an Array Game",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-winner-of-an-array-game/",
      category: "Pointers",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-the-winner-of-an-array-game.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-05"),
    },
    {
      question: "Seat Reservation Manager",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/seat-reservation-manager/",
      category: "Priority Queue",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "seat-reservation-manager.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-06"),
    },
    {
      question: "Eliminate Maximum Number of Monsters",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/eliminate-maximum-number-of-monsters/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "eliminate-maximum-number-of-monsters.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-07"),
    },
    {
      question: "Determine if a Cell Is Reachable at a Given Time",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/determine-if-a-cell-is-reachable-at-a-given-time/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "determine-if-a-cell-is-reachable-at-a-given-time.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-08"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count Number of Homogenous Substrings",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-number-of-homogenous-substrings/",
      category: "Pointers",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "count-number-of-homogenous-substrings.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-09"),
    },
    {
      question: "Restore the Array From Adjacent Pairs",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/restore-the-array-from-adjacent-pairs/",
      category: "Graph",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "restore-the-array-from-adjacent-pairs.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-10"),
    },
    {
      question: "Design Graph With Shortest Path Calculator",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-graph-with-shortest-path-calculator/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "design-graph-with-shortest-path-calculator.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-11"),
    },
    {
      question: "Bus Routes",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/bus-routes/",
      category: "Advanced Graph",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "bus-routes.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-12"),
    },
    {
      question: "Sort Vowels in a String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-vowels-in-a-string/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "sort-vowels-in-a-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-13"),
    },
    {
      question: "Unique Length-3 Palindromic Subsequences",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-length-3-palindromic-subsequences/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "unique-length-3-palindromic-subsequences.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-14"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Element After Decreasing and Rearranging",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-element-after-decreasing-and-rearranging/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-element-after-decreasing-and-rearranging.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-15"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Unique Binary String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-unique-binary-string/",
      category: "Backtracking",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "find-unique-binary-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-16"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimize Maximum Pair Sum in Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimize-maximum-pair-sum-in-array/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimize-maximum-pair-sum-in-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-17"),
    },
    {
      question: "Frequency of the Most Frequent Element",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/frequency-of-the-most-frequent-element/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "frequency-of-the-most-frequent-element.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-18"),
    },
    {
      question: "Reduction Operations to Make the Array Elements Equal",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reduction-operations-to-make-the-array-elements-equal/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "reduction-operations-to-make-the-array-elements-equal.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-19"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Amount of Time to Collect All Apples in a Tree",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-amount-of-time-to-collect-garbage/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-amount-of-time-to-collect-garbage.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-20"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count Nice Pairs in an Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-nice-pairs-in-an-array/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "count-nice-pairs-in-an-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-21"),
    },
    {
      question: "Diagonal Traverse II",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/diagonal-traverse-ii/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "diagonal-traverse-ii.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-22"),
    },
    {
      question: "Arithmetic Subarrays",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/arithmetic-subarrays/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "arithmetic-subarrays.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-23"),
    },
    {
      question: "Maximum Number of Coins You Can Get",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-absolute-differences-in-a-sorted-array/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "maximum-number-of-coins-you-can-get.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-24"),
    },
    {
      question: "Sum of Absolute Differences in a Sorted Array",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-absolute-differences-in-a-sorted-array/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "sum-of-absolute-differences-in-a-sorted-array.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-25"),
    },
    {
      question: "Largest Submatrix With Rearrangements",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-submatrix-with-rearrangements/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "largest-submatrix-with-rearrangements.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-26"),
    },
    {
      question: "Knight Dialer",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/knight-dialer/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "knight-dialer.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-27"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of Ways to Divide a Long Corridor",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-ways-to-divide-a-long-corridor/",
      category: "Dynamic Programming",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "number-of-ways-to-divide-a-long-corridor.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-28"),
    },
    {
      question: "Number of 1 Bits",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-1-bits/",
      category: "Bit Manipulation",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "number-of-1-bits.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-29"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum One Bit Operations to Make Integers Zero",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-one-bit-operations-to-make-integers-zero/",
      category: "Bit Manipulation",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      solution: "minimum-one-bit-operations-to-make-integers-zero.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-11-30"),
    },
    {
      question: "Check If Two String Arrays are Equivalent",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-two-string-arrays-are-equivalent/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "check-if-two-string-arrays-are-equivalent.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-12-01"),
    },
    {
      question: "Find Words That Can Be Formed by Characters",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-words-that-can-be-formed-by-characters/",
      category: "Arrays & Hashing",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "find-words-that-can-be-formed-by-characters.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-12-02"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Time Visiting All Points",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-time-visiting-all-points/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "minimum-time-visiting-all-points.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-12-03"),
    },
    {
      question: "Minimum Number of Coins to be Added",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-coins-to-be-added/",
      category: "Greedy",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      solution: "minimum-number-of-coins-to-be-added.py",
    },
    {
      question: "Largest 3 Same Digit Number in String",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-3-same-digit-number-in-string/",
      category: "Sliding Window",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "largest-3-same-digit-number-in-string.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-12-04"),
    },
    {
      question: "Count of Matches in Tournament",
      link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-of-matches-in-tournament/",
      category: "Math",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      solution: "count-of-matches-in-tournament.py",
      dailyChallenge: new Date("2023-12-05"),
    },
  ];

export default tableData;